Fraser W Levack

Full Time 3rd Year Computer Science Student.

Contact.

2/3, 50 Kelvingrove St Glasgow, G3 7RZ 07724349134

Email LinkedIn GitHub

Education

3rd year, BSC in Computer Science University of Glasgow

Scottish Advanced Higher A x 2 Scottish Higher A x 5 From Grove Academy Dundee

Programming Languages

Typescript
Python
Java
C & C++
HTML & CSS

Technologies

React Django Vite Node.js, Deno & Three.js SDL & OpenGL

Tools

GitHub & GitLab JetBrains IDE's WSL Unix / Ubuntu Pages & Workflows

About

I am a 3rd year Glasgow University undergraduate student living in Glasgow. I am an enthusiastic individual with a wide range of software experience. I have excellent communication skills and a positive attitude. My interests vary a lot, from low level programming to front end frameworks.

Experience

AUGUST 2024 - PRESENT

Freelance Web Developer | Design for Displacement Lead developer for the Design for Displacement architecture course. Working with Typescript and React to create a stylistic, modern and informative Website.

SEPTEMBER 2024 - PRESENT

Software Developer & Team Chair | Off Axis Gigs Working in a team, through Glasgow Uni, to design and implement improvements to the company's current tech system.

SEPTEMBER 2020 – SEPTEMBER 2024

Pharmacy Assistant | Davidson's Chemists Long-term part-time job, using pharmaceutical technologies.

SEPTEMBER 2021 – JUNE 2022

Lifeguard | Ye Amphibious Ancients Bathing Association Dedicated Pool lifeguard.

Projects

Django Jam | Music Sharing

An online web-app with an interactive piano. Used to record and share Tunes with others.

C Paint | Painting Software

A program written C and using OpenGL to allow painting.

Sled-Eval | Evaluation Library

A C library for evaluating mathematical expressions. Detailed and easy to use.

Awards, Societies and Hobbies

Awards: – Vice Chief Executive for MATE National Competition – World Host Principles Customer Service, – DVSA Driver's License – NPLQ Lifeguard – Grove Academy Vice School Captain

Member of: Glasgow Uni Tech, Ai, and Book Societies Some other hobbies include Surfing, Skiing and rock climbing.